Everybody! Central Perk is proud to present...
各位请安静,中央公园很荣幸为各位介绍
...the music of Miss Phoebe Buffay.
……菲比小姐的音乐
Thanks.
谢谢，
I wanna start with a song that's about that moment...
首先我想从一首...
...when you suddenly realize what life is really all about.
有关顿悟人生那一刻的歌……开始
Okay,here we go.
开始罗...
Okay. Thank you very much.
非常感谢
Oh,great. This is just
什么?这下可好
The One With The Blackout
六人行 第1季 第07集 纽约大停电
-=BT之家DRM小组 http://bbs.btbbt.com=- 荣誉出品 河马根据网络字幕微调制作
This is so cool,you guys. The entire city's blacked out.
这简直是酷毙了 纽约大停电
It's all of Manhattan. They have no idea...
我妈说是整个布鲁克林 外加部份曼哈顿和皇后区
...when it's back on.
不知何时恢复电力
-You guys,this is big. -Pants and a sweater. Why,Mom?
-这可真是大停电 -裤子和毛衣,为什么,妈?
Who will I meet in a blackout?
停电我能去见谁?
Power-company guys? Eligible looters?
电力公司的人? 单身的趁火打劫之徒?
-Can we talk about this later? Okay. -Can I borrow the phone?
-以后再聊，好吗? -电话能借我吗?
I wanna call my apartment and check on my grandma.
我想打回住处 确定我祖母是否安好
What's my number?
等等，我的电话几号?
I never call me.
我从未打电话给自己过
Oh,my God! It's her. It's that Victoria 's Secret model.
天啊，是她 维多利亚的秘密(内衣品牌)的模特儿
Something Goodacre.
叫…古亚克的
Hi,Mom,it's Jill.
妈，我是洁儿
She 's right. It's Jill. Jill Goodacre. Oh,my God!
没错，洁儿 洁儿.古亚克.天哪!
I am trapped in an A TM vestibule with Jill Goodacre.
没想到我和洁儿.古亚克同时被困在提款机室
Is it a vestibule? Maybe it's an atrium.
是小室还是正厅?
Yeah,that is the part to focus on,you idiot.
那才是值得注意的对象，笨蛋
I' m fine. I' m just stuck at the bank in an ATM vestibule.
对，我没事只是被困在银行提款机室
Jill says vestibule, I'm going with vestibule.
洁儿说小室? 那我也说小室
I' m fine. No,l' m not alone.
我没事,不,旁边有人
I don't know,some guy.
我不认识,某人
Oh,some guy. I am some guy.
某人?行,某人
Jill,I saw you with some guy last night.
洁儿，我昨晚看见你和某人在一起
Yes,he was some guy.
没错，他是某人.
Hey,everyone.
各位
Officiating at tonight's blackout is Rabbi T ribbiani.
今晚主持停电晚会的 是崔比安尼拉此
Chandler's old roommate was Jewish. These are our only candles.
钱德的老室友是个犹太人 我们只剩这些蜡烛
So happy Hanukkah!
祝各位光明节快乐
Look! Ugly Naked Guy lit a bunch of candles.
瞧，丑陋裸男点燃点几根蜡烛
That had to hurt!
一定很痛
All right,all right! It's been 14 1/2 minutes...
已过了14分30秒
...and you still haven 't said one word. God!
……你却连一字也没说
Do something! Just make contact. Smile!
争气点，打破沈闷，微笑
There you go.
效果不错
You 're definitely scaring her.
算了吧，你正在吓她
Hello? Oh,hi,Mom.
喂? 妈妈.
Mom.
妈.
Mom,you' re tripping!
妈妈,你内急!
Dexter's a dog. The blackout's scaring him.
德特是一条狗 大停电把他吓坏了
You'd pee in Dad's shoes too if you didn't know.
如果你不知道 你也可以尿在爸爸的鞋子里.
All right,call me back.
好吧，给我回电话
-Mothers. -Yeah.
-妈妈. -是的.
Attaboy! A word.
好小伙!一个词.
That wasn 't so hard. Mothers. Yeah!
这样不坏.妈妈，是的！
Mothers. Yeah! Perfect.
妈妈，是的！完美
Don 't smile.
不要笑.
Would you like to call somebody?
你需要给别人打电话吗?
Yeah,about 300 guys I went to high school with.
是的，和我一起上大学的300个小伙
Yeah,thanks.
是的，谢了.
-Hello? -It's me.
-你好? -是我
-It's Chandler. Are you okay? -Yeah,l' m fine.
-是钱德,你好吗? -我还好
I' m stuck in an ATM vestibule...
我被困在提款机室...
...with Jill Goodacre.
和洁儿吉亚克一起
-What? -l' m stuck...
-什么? -我被困在...
...in an ATM vestibule...
...提款机室了...
...with Jill Goodacre.
...和洁儿吉亚克一起
I have no idea what you said.
我听不懂你在说什么
Put Joey on the phone.
叫乔伊听电话
-What's up,man? -l' m stuck...
-怎么了? -我被困在...
...in an ATM vestibule...
...提款机室了...
...with Jill Goodacre!
...和洁儿吉亚克一起
Oh,my God!
噢,我的天那
He's trapped in an ATM vestibule with Jill Goodacre!
他和洁儿吉亚克被困在提款机室
Chandler,listen.
钱德，听著…
Like that thought never entered my mind.
别以为我没这个念头
-Okay. -Somebody.
换人，快
-I'll go. I'll go. -Okay.
好吧，换我
Senior year of college, on a pool table.
大四在撞球台上
-Pool table? -That's my sister.
-撞球台上? -这就是我妹啦
Okay,my weirdest place would have to be...
我最奇怪的地方是在...
...the women's room of the New York City Public Library.
...纽约市立图书馆二楼女厕
Oh,my God! What were you doing in a library?
拜托，你去图书馆干什么
-Pheebs,what about you? -Oh,Milwaukee.
-菲此，你呢? -密尔瓦基
It's a really weird place.
真是一个奇怪的地方.
Ross?
罗斯?
Disneyland,1 989. " It's a small world after all. "
迪士尼，1989年小小世界
No way.
不可能…
The ride broke down...
机器故障
...so Carol and I went behind those mechanical Dutch children.
所以我和卡萝就到荷兰机器儿童后面
We were asked never to return to the Magic Kingdom.
他们好死不死正巧修好机器… 从此他们禁止我们再到奇幻王国去
Let's see,that leaves....
好吧,只有……
-Rachel? -Come on,I already went.
-瑞秋? -拜托，我说过了
-You did not go. -I did.
-你才没那 -我说过了
T ell us. Come on.
快点告诉我们
All right,the weirdest place would have to be...
好吧，最奇怪的地方是...
...the foot of the bed.
...床脚
-Step back! -We have a winner!
-一句 -我们今晚有优胜了
This must be what the fridge looks like with the door closed.
这就是冰箱关上时候的样子
Spooky.
恐怕.
Anybody hungry? We got a Klondike...soup.
有人饿了吗?我们有科隆迪克……汤
I've never had a relationship with that kind of passion.
我从来没有那种关系也没那种感受
Where you have to have somebody even in a theme park.
在主题乐园中你忽然欲火中烧
It was the only thing to do that didn't have a line.
当时只有这件事可做
Barry wouldn't even kiss me on a miniature golf course.
巴瑞连在打迷你高尔夫时 也不肯亲我
-Come on. -No.
-不是吧 -是的
He said we held up the people behind us.
他说这样会耽误后面的人
You didn't marry him because...?
你逃婚的原因是…
Do you think there are people that go through life...
你认为有人这辈子没有过那种…
... never having that kind of...?
……从来没有过……
-Probably. -Really?
-也许吧. -真的?
I'll tell you something. Passion is way overrated.
但是我得告诉你 激情被过度重视.
-Yeah,right. -lt is.
-没错 -是的
Eventually,it kind of burns out.
最后激情很快就退去
But hopefully what you're left with is trust and security and....
但双方仍保有信赖，安全感和...
In my ex-wife's case, lesbianism.
以我前妻为例…女同志主义
For those people who miss out on that passion thing...
因此,缺乏激情之人还是有……
...there's other stuff.
……其他可取之处的
-Okay. -But I don't think that'll be you.
但我想你不是那种人
-You don't? -See,I see...
-你认为我不是? -我...
-... big passion in your future. -Really?
-对你的未来将充满激情 -真的?
-You do? -I do.
-你真的这样认为 -没错
Ross,you' re so great.
罗斯，你真是太了不起了
It's never gonna happen.
不可能发生的
-What? -You and Rachel.
-什么? -你和瑞秋
What? Me and Ra?
Why not?
为什么?
You waited too long to make your move...
因为你拖太久才行动
...and now you' re in the "friend zone. "
现在只能待在“朋友区”
-l' m not in the zone. -No,Ross. You' re mayor of the zone.
-不，我没在朋友区 -罗斯，你是朋友区主席
Look,l' m taking my time,all right? I' m laying the groundwork.
我在静观其变，行吗? 我正在为以后铺路
Every day I get a little bit closer to
我每天往前推进一点
Priesthood!
圣人
I'm telling you,she has no idea what you're thinking.
告诉你,罗斯,她根本不知道你在想什么
She just ran her fingers through my hair.
她刚刚用她的手指缕我的头发.
-Were you missing that interaction? -No,no,no.
-你怀念那种作用力吗? -不,不,不.
This is running fingers through your hair,okay?
这才是缕你的头发.
Now this is a tousle.
这不过是弄乱你的头发罢了.
If you don't ask her out soon, you'll be in the zone forever.
如果再不快点约她出去 你将困在朋友区永远无法脱身
I will,I will. I'm waiting for the right moment.
我会的 我只是在等恰当的时机
What?
什么?
-What,now? -Yeah.
-什么,现在? -是的.
What's messing you up? The wine? The moonlight?
你缺什么? 美酒?烛光?月光?
You gotta go up to her and say, " Look,Rachel,l"
你只需走到她面前说 瑞秋，我想你…
-What? -We' re shushing...
-什么? -我们在嘘……
... because we' re trying to hear something.
……因为我们正在听
-What? What? -Don't you hear that?
-因为我们正在听 -难道你没听见?
See?
听见没?
-Would you like gum? -ls it sugarless?
-想来片口香糖吗? -无糖的吗?
-Sorry,it's not. -Then no,thanks.
-抱歉，不是 -不，谢了
What was that?
你在搞什么东西?
Mental note: If Jill Goodacre offers you gum,you take it.
切记!洁儿请你吃口香糖你就吃
If she offers you mangled animal carcass,you take it!
她叫你吃动物死尸 你也得吃
New York City has no power
纽约大停电
And the milk is getting sour
牛奶变酸
But to me it is not scary
不过没关系
Because I stay away from dairy
因为我不喝牛奶
-Here goes. -You'll do it?
-你决定啦? -我决定了
-I'll do it. -Want help?
-我决定了 -需要帮助吗?
You come out,you' re a dead man.
如果你想当电灯泡你就死定了
-Good luck,man. -Thanks.
--罗斯…祝你幸运 -谢谢.
-Okay. -Okay.
-Okay.
Where you going? You can't go out there.
你要去哪里? 不行，你不能去外面
-Why not? -Because of the reason.
-为什么? -因为有理由
-That would be? -I can't tell you.
-那是什么? -不能告诉你
Joey,what's going on?
乔伊，到底怎么了?
You gotta promise you'll never tell Ross that I told you.
好吧，但你得答应我 不会告诉罗斯是我说的
-What? -He's planning your birthday party.
-说什么? -他正在准备你的生日舞会
-Oh,my God! I love him! -You better act surprised.
-天啊，我爱他 -你最好装成一副吃惊的样子
-About what? -My surprise party.
-装什么? -我的生日舞会
-What surprise party? -Oh,stop it. Joey already told me.
-什么生日舞会? -少装蒜了,乔伊已经告诉我了
He didn't tell me.
他没有告诉我
Don't look at me. This is Ross' thing.
别看我，这是罗斯的主意
This is typical. I'm always the last to know.
每次都这样,我总是最后知道的人
You are not. We tell you stuff.
你不是，我们都有告诉你是哦
I was the last one to know when Chandler got bit by the peacock.
钱德在动物园被孔雀咬 我是最后知道的人
I was the last to know you had a crush on Joey.
也是最后知道乔伊刚搬来时 你对他有意思的人
What?
什么?
Looks like I was second to last.
看来我是倒数第二
You had a crush on me?
你对我有意思?
All right. It wasn't a crush, it was a dent.
好吧,这不算是有意思,是有点印象.
Big dent?
很深的印象?
You were moving your furniture. I thought you had nice arms.
你动了我的家具 我想你的胳膊不错,仅此而已.
Nice arms,huh?
胳膊不错?
Hey,Mon,l' m moving the chair.
嘿,莫妮卡,我在搬动椅子哦.
Do anything for you?
你感觉怎么样？
With all the lights out you can actually see the stars.
所有的灯都灭了,你才可以真正的看到星星啊.
It's so nice.
真不错.
I have a question.
我有个问题
Actually,it's not so much a question.
也谈不上是问题
It's more of a general wondering....
只是……
ment.
好奇.
-Okay. -Okay. Here it goes.
-好吧 -好吧,是这样的.
Well,for a while now, I've been wanting to....
这些日子以来我一直想…
-Yes,that's right. -Look at that little kitty!
-对，没错 -瞧那只小猫!
What?
什么?
Top of the world Looking down on creation
And the only explanation I can find
Is the love that I found Ever since you 've been around
All right,this is just Bactine. It won't hurt.
好吧,这只是药不会痛的
-Ow! -Sorry,that was wax.
-噢! -对不起，那是蜡油
Poor little T ooty's scared. We should find his owner.
可怜的小猫快吓死了 我们得找到它的主人
Why not put poor T ooty in the hall?
何不将它放在走廊?
During a blackout? She'll get trampled.
大停电时?它会被踩死的
Yeah?
是吗?
Damage control. Get back to the gum.
亡羊补牢.口香糖是绝佳的选择
Gum would be perfection.
口香糖是绝佳的选择
Gum would be perfection?
口香糖是绝佳的选择?
Gum would be perfection.
口香糖是绝佳的选择
Could've said, "Gum would be nice. " But,no.
我大可说”我也来一片”,但不，
For me,gum is perfection.
我说的是"口香糖是绝佳的选择"
I loathe myself!
我真鄙视我自己
Oh,no,they' re nuns. They hate all living things.
不，她们是修女,讨厌一切生物
Hi. We just found this cat, and we' re looking for the owner.
我们刚捡到这只猫 目前正在找它的主人
Yeah,it's mine.
猫是我的
-He seems to hate you. Are you sure? -It's my cat. Give me my cat.
-可是它似乎很讨厌你 -确定，猫是我的，把猫给我
-Wait a minute. What's his name? -Bob Buttons.
-等等，它叫什么名字? -鲍伯钮扣
-Bob Buttons? -Bob Buttons. Here,Bob Buttons.
--鲍伯钮扣? -鲍伯钮扣,过来,鲍伯钮扣
You are a very bad man!
你真是个大坏蛋
You owe me a cat.
你们欠我一只猫
Here,kitty,kitty,kitty.
来这, 咪咪, 咪咪, 咪咪.
Here,kitty,kitty.
Where did you go,little kitty?
小猫咪…你上哪儿去了?
IKitty,kitty,kitty. Come here,kitty,kitty.
小猫咪,过来.
-Hi. -Buona sera.
-Hi. -Buona sera. (意大利语)
Wow!
喔!
Mon,wanna go for a ride in my racecar?
莫妮卡,愿意搭我的跑车去兜风吗?
I'll bring my arms.
我会带我的胳膊一起去的.
We can bring my wheelbarrow for your teeth!
我们为你的牙齿准备独轮车!
Come on,lucky sixes!
来吧，幸运六
Everybody,this is Paolo.
各位，他是保罗
Paolo,I want you to meet my friends. This is Monica...
保罗，向你介绍我的朋友 这位是摩妮卡
-Hi. -...and Joey...
-Hi -……这位是乔伊……
-Hi. -...and Ross.
-Hi -……还有罗斯……
Hi.
He doesn't speak much English.
他不太会讲英语
Monopoly!
大富翁
Look at that!
看啊!
So,where did Paolo come from?
那,保罗来自哪里?
Italy,I think.
我猜是意大利
No,I mean tonight. Suddenly,into our lives.
不，我是指今晚,这栋公寓? 突然介入我们的生活?
That cat turned out to be Paolo's cat. Isn't that funny?
那只猫结果是保罗的 这不是很有意思吗?
That is funny. And Rachel keeps touching him.
真有意思,而且瑞秋不断摸他
I looked all over and couldn't find the kitty anywhere.
我找遍了整栋公寓,但就是找不到猫
I found him. It was Paolo's cat.
我找到了，是保罗的猫
Well,there you go. Last to know again.
瞧，我又是最后一个知道
And I'm guessing,this is Paolo?
由于没人告诉我,我猜他就是保罗
Paolo,this is Phoebe.
保罗，她叫菲比
You betcha!
You betcha!（意大利语）
All right. Okay. What next?
没错,下一步呢?
Blow a bubble. A bubble's good.
吹泡泡,吹泡泡不错.
It's got a boyish charm. It's impish.
可以很好展现男性魅力，顽皮的一面
Here we go.
来吧
Nice going,imp!
吹得可真好…
It's okay. All I need to do...
不要紧,我只需把手伸过去
...is reach over and put it back in my mouth.
将它放回口中
Good save! We 're back on track and I'm...
救得好,现在我已重回轨道
... chewing someone else 's gum.
而且还嚼著别人的口香糖
This is not my gum! Oh,my God! Oh,my God!
这不是我的口香糖,天哪,我的天啊!
And now you 're choking.
很好,现在你呛到了
You all right?
你没事吧
My God! You' re choking!
天呀,你呛到了
-Better? -Yes.
-感觉好点没? -好多了
Thank you. That was....
谢谢，那真是…
-That was.... -Perfection?
-那真是… -绝佳的选择?
That was no tousle.
这可不是把头发弄乱而已
-What'd he say that was so funny? -I have absolutely no idea.
-他讲什么,他讲什么 -我完全搞不懂
That's classic.
女人都这样
My God,you guys! What am I doing? This is so un-me!
天啊，我在干什么? 这太不像我了
If you want,I'll do it.
不介意的话我要上了
I just wanna bite his bottom lip.
我只想咬他的下嘴唇
But I won't.
但我不会这么做的
The first time he smiled at me...
他第一次对我微笑时
...those seconds were more exciting than weeks with Barry.
那三秒钟比我和巴瑞 在百慕达得三个礼拜还令我兴奋
Did you rent mopeds?
你骑机踏车吗?
Because I've heard Oh,it's not about that right now.
因为我听说…我离题了
I know it's superficial, and we have nothing in common...
我知道这样很肤浅 而且我们毫无共通点
...and we don't even speak the same language,but,God!
连语言也不通但...
-Paolo,hi. -Ross.
-保罗 -罗斯
Listen....
听着
Listen,something you should know.
有件事你该了解
Rachel and I are....
瑞秋和我
We' re kind of a thing.
有那么一点
-Thing? -Thing. Yes,thing.
-一点? -一点.是的,一点
-You have the sex? -No.
-你们做爱没有？ -没有.
No,technically the sex is not being had. But that's....
技术上而言，还没做爱
But that's not the point.
但这不是重点
The point is that Rachel and I should be....
重点是瑞秋和我应该…
Well,Rachel and l should be together.
瑞秋和我应该在一起
And if you get in the
你来到
-ln bed -No.
-床上? -不是
No,not where I was going.
不是，我不是指那个
If you get in the way of us becoming a thing...
如果你让我们无法结台
...then I would be,well,very sad.
我会非常…难过
So,do you...?
所以, 你……
-So you do know a little English? -Little.
-你懂一点英文 -会一点
-Do you know the word "crap-weasel "? -No.
-你懂什么叫“二百五” -不懂
That's funny. You are a huge crap-weasel.
不懂?真好笑 因为你就是个超级二百五
We've been doing this for an hour. It's easy.
我们已玩了一小时,很简单的
Ready?
准备好没?
Okay? Now try it.
试试看
You gotta whip it.
不，你该拍一下
Look,look. The last candle's about to burn out.
看，最后一根蜡烛就要燃尽
T en,nine,eight,seven...
10，9，8，7
... minus 46,minus 47, minus 48....
46分钟，-47分钟，-48分钟・，．
-Thank you. -Thanks.
-谢谢 -谢谢
IKind of spooky without any lights.
没有灯光有点恐怖
Okay,guys,I have the definitive one.
停，我这个最逼真
This probably isn't the best time to bring it up...
罗斯，现在提并不恰当
...but you have to throw a party for Monica.
但你得为摩尼卡开个舞会
-This has been fun. -Yes.
-玩得真开心 -对
Thanks for letting me use your phone...
谢谢你的手机
...and for saving my life.
并救了我的命
Well,goodbye,Chandler. I had a great blackout.
再见了，钱德 此次停电我玩得很开心
See you.
再见
Hi,l' m account number 71 43457.
我的帐号是7143457
I don't know if you got that...
我不知道你有没有录到
... but I would really like a copy of the tape.
但我想要这一卷录影带